得了  你俩都死多少次了
Come on, how many times did you two die anyway?
有个人的力量远强于米迦勒
There is someone besides Michael
他能够对付路西法
strong enough to take on Lucifer.
是谁
Who's that?
上帝
God.
我要找到上帝
I'm gonna find god.
你想要什么
What is it you want?
一个护身符
An amulet.
在上帝附近会有剧烈反应
It burns hot in god's presence.
能够帮助我找到他
It'll help me find him.
这我可没有
I don't have something like that.
你是没有
You don't.
这是什么
What is it?
鲍比叔叔给我的  说是这东西很特别
Uncle Bobby gave it to me. Said it was real special.
谢谢  萨姆  我很喜欢
Thank you, Sam. I love it.
-能借我吗  - 不要
- May I borrow it?  - No.
迪恩  给我
Dean. Give it to me.
可别弄丢了
Don't lose it.
(如今)
在找这个吗
Looking for this?
早啊
Mornin'.
闭嘴  举起手来
Shut up. Hands where I can see 'em.
等等
Wait a minute.
罗伊  是你吗
Is that you, Roy?
果然是啊
It is, isn't it?
那你就是沃尔特了
Which makes you Walt.
好啊  沃尔特
Hiya, Walt.
面罩没用了
Don't matter.
是我多心了吗  你俩好像有点不高兴啊
Well, is it just me, or do you two seem a tad upset?
萨姆  你造成了天启
You think you can flip the switch on the apocalypse
还以为自己能一走了之吗
and just walk away, Sam?
你听谁说的
Who told you that?
可不止是我们在追捕你们
We ain't the only hunters after you.
下辈子见了
See you in the next life.
听我说  让我解释一下好吗
Hear me out. I can explain, okay?
拜托
Please.
别动
Stay the hell down.
杀了他
Shoot him.
杀死萨姆是没错  但是迪恩的话...
Killing Sam was right, but Dean --
我们别无选择  我们杀了他弟弟  你个白痴
He made us, and we just snuffed his brother, you idiot.
难道你想下半辈子
You want to spend the rest of your life
都笼罩在被迪恩·温彻斯特追杀的阴影下吗
knowing Dean Winchester's on your ass?
我可不想
'cause I don't.
杀了他
Shoot him.
来吧  罗伊  动手吧
Go ahead, Roy. Do it.
但我可警告你
But I'm gonna warn you --
老子一旦回来
when I come back...
你可就死惨了
I'm gonna be pissed.
快啊
Come on!
要杀就杀
Let's get this show on the road.
你不来我来
Come on, already.
[邪恶力量 第5季第16集]
小萨姆
Sammy?
快来啊
Come on! Let's go!
这什么怪梦啊
Weird dream.
有火吗
Got your lighter?
哇哦  我已经好多年没见过这个了
Whoa. I haven't seen this in years.
点火吧
Fire 'em up.
这我记得
I remember this.
那是1996年的国庆日
That's 4th of July, 1996.
爸爸从不允许我们这么做
Dad would never let us do anything like this.
谢谢  迪恩  这太棒了
Thanks, Dean. This is great.
要爆炸啦
Fire in the hole!
萨姆
Sam?
迪恩
Dean.
卡西
Cass?
是我
Yeah, it's me.
你能别偷窥我的清梦了好不
You got to stop poking around in my dreams.
我也有隐私啊
I need some "Me" Time.
好好听清楚
Listen to me very closely.
这不是梦
This isn't a dream.
那这是啥
Then what is it?
其实你心里早就知道了
Deep down, you already know.
我死了
I'm dead.
节哀
Condolences.
我在哪儿
Where am I?
天堂
Heaven.
啥
Heaven?
我怎么会到天堂来的
How did I get to heaven?
请你听好
Please, listen.
这个能让我你谈话的咒语很难维持
This spell, this connection -- it's difficult to maintain.
要是我在天堂
Wait -- I-if I'm in heaven...
萨姆哪儿去了
Then where's Sam?
你看到了什么
What do you see?
你啥意思
What do you mean, what do I see?
有人看到的是隧道或者一条河
Some people see a tunnel or a river.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
我看到仪表板  我在车里  在一条路上
Nothing. M-my dash. I'm in my car. I'm on a road.
好吧  一条路
All right -- a road.
你的话看到的是一条路
For you, it's a road.
沿着路往前走  迪恩  你就会找到萨姆
Follow it, Dean. You'll find Sam.
沿着...
Follow --
这条路
...road.
多谢
Thank you.
萨姆
So, Sam...
听说你刚到麦金利
I hear you're new to McKinley.
是的  先生  才到两周
Um, yes, sir -- two weeks.
史黛芬妮一直说起你
Stephanie over here just can't seem
简直是说个没完
to stop talking about you.
爸  别说了
Dad, shut up!
那个...啥
Just...wow.
迪恩
Dean?
你怎么会在我梦里
What are you doing in my dream?
你爸爸是干什么的
So, what does your father do for a living?
是嘛
Hmm. You don't say.
天堂
Heaven?
是啊
Yep.
好吧  我们怎么会到天堂的
Okay, how are we in heaven?
我们一直在降妖除魔嘛
All that clean living, I guess.
不不  好吧
No, no. Um...Okay.
你的话我能明白
You, I get. Sure.
但为什么我也在
But me?
你可能没意识到
Maybe you haven't noticed, but, um...
但我做过的那些事...
I've...done a few things.
你当时以为做的是好事
You thought you were doing the right thing.
据我所知  该不该上天堂的标准
Last I checked, it wasn't the road to heaven
不是初衷  而是后果
that was paved with good intentions.
这里要是天国  天国可真逊
Yeah, well, if this is the skymall, it sucks.
3P和塑胶娃娃在哪里
I mean, where's the triplets and the latex, you know?
人可是有需求的
Come on. A guy has needs.
知道吗  据说人挂了之后
You know, when you bite dust,
许多过往的记忆会在眼前闪过
they say your life flashes before your eyes.
什么意思
Your point?
这幢房子  是我的回忆之一
This house ... it's one of my memories.
我醒过来的时候  也是在自己的记忆里
When I woke up, I woke up in one of my memories...
国庆日那天我们放烟花把一片草地给烧了
the 4th of July that we burned down that field.
或许天堂就是这样
Well, maybe that's what heaven is...
让你再一次经历你最光荣的时刻
A place where you relive your greatest hits.
等下  这么说  在里面跟牙套女调情
Wait... so, playing footsie with brace-face in there,
是你的得意时刻咯
t-that... that's a trophy moment for you?
迪恩  我那时候才11岁
Dean, I was 11 years old.
这是我第一个像样的感恩节
This was my first real Thanksgiving.
说什么呢  我们每年都过感恩节
What are you talking about? We had Thanksgiving every year.
无非是一桶鸡块
We had a bucket of extra-crispy,
还有老爸坐在沙发上睡死过去
and dad passed out on the couch.
我不记得有这个
I don't remember this.
-我们应该...  - 当然
- We should, uh... - Yeah, definitely.
好吧
Okay.
刚才那是怎么回事
Uh, what the hell was that?
不清楚  不过待会儿下楼要坐扶梯
I don't know, but we are taking the escalator back downstairs.
卡西
Cass!
你这是做什么
What are you doing?
你看像做什么
What's it look like?
像是你疯了
Like you've lost your mind.
卡西之前就用收音机
Cass talked to me before
跟我"长途"通话的  所以
Using this... this "Phone home" radio thing, so I...
卡西
Cass!
我听到了
I can hear you.
卡西
Cass? Hey.
我找到萨姆了  但刚才发生一件事
So, uh, so, I found Sam, b-but something just happened.
有一束奇怪的光柱
There was this weird beam of light...
别让光照到你
Don't go into the light.
好的  多谢  卡洛琳
Okay. Thanks... Caroline.
那是什么
What was it?
不是什么  是谁
Not what... who.
是撒迦利亚  他在找你们
Zachariah. He's searching for you.
如过被他找到会怎样
A-and if he finds us?
你们死了是没法让米迦勒和路西法附身的
You can't say "Yes" To Michael and Lucifer if you're dead,
所以撒迦利亚必须让你们复活
So Zachariah needs to return you to your bodies.
很好  这不完事儿了
Great. Problem solved.
不  你不懂  你们已经到了天堂
No, you don't understand. Y-you're behind the wall.
这是个绝佳的机遇
This is a rare opportunity.
什么机遇
For what?
你要去找一个天使  他叫约书亚
You need to find an angel. His name is Joshua.
老兄  无意冒犯
Hey, man, no offense,
但是我们这儿天使多得要死了
But we are kind of ass-full of angels, okay?
-你去找吧  - 我不能
- You find him. - I can't.
我回不去天堂
I can't return to heaven.
约书亚怎么了
So, what's so important about Joshua?
有传言说  他能跟上帝交谈
The rumor is, he talks to God.
那又怎样
And? So?
你难道不觉得  我们至少  至少应当知道
You think maybe, just maybe, we should find out
上帝到底怎么想的吗
what the hell God has been saying?
他火了哎
Geez. Touchy.
请你们  沿着主轴走
Please. I just need you to follow the road.
什么主轴
What road?
它被称作世界的轴心
It's called the axis mundi.
是纵贯天堂的一条路
It's a path that runs through heaven.
在不同的人眼中  它有不同的形态
Different people see it as different things.
你们看到的是双车道公路
For you, it's two-lane asphalt.
主轴会引领你们到达花园
The road will lead you to the garden.
在那里  你们会找到约书亚
You'll find Joshua there.
约书亚  他能带我们去找上帝
And Joshua... He can take us to God.
花园
The garden.
抓紧时间
Please. Hurry.
你怎么看
So, w-what do you think?
我看我们就把墙砸碎  把约书亚猫捉出来咯
I think we hit the yellow bricks, find this Joshua cat.
真的
Really?
你不这么想
What, you don't?
我自然是  只是惊讶你也愿意
No, I, uh, I'm just surprised you do.
我是说  你之前一直想揍上帝一顿呢
I mean, last I checked, you wanted to break God's nose.
现在你认为他能帮我们了
Now you think he can help?
只有他能帮我们
He's the only one who can.
好了  萨姆  我们都光荣牺牲了
I mean, come on, Sam. We are royally boned.
所以  祈祷
So, prayer...
是绝望者最后的希望了
A last hope of a desperate man.
外面不是路来着吗
Wasn't there a street out here?
原本是的
There was.
迪恩
Dean?
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
找主轴啊
Looking for a road.
主轴会在衣柜里吗
You... you think the road is in a closet?
萨姆  这里可是天堂
We're in heaven, Sam, okay?
记忆成了现实  卡西上了电视
Our memories are coming true, Cass is on TV.
衣柜里找条主轴出来
Finding a road in a closet would be pretty much
那可要算今天最正常的事了
The most normal thing to happen to us today.
怎么了
What?
我小的时候
I used to have one of these...
有个一模一样的
When I was a kid.
这就是主轴吗
That was the road?
我猜是
I guess.
够梦幻的哈
Pretty trippy, right?
是啊
Yeah.
更梦幻的是
More trippy...
很显然
Um...Apparently...
你"要抱抱"
You "Wuv hugz."
闭嘴
Shut up.
等下  我知道我们在哪儿了
Wait a minute. I know where we are.
哪儿
Where?
我们在家里
We're home.
迪恩
Dean.
迪恩  饿不饿
Hey, Dean, you hungry?
面包皮要切掉吗
You want the crusts cut off?
要  我喜欢
Yeah, I... I'd love that.
妈
Mom?
看来这不是你的记忆  萨姆
I guess it's not your memory, Sam.
抱歉
Sorry.
迪恩
Dean, uh...
我们应该
we should...go --
继续寻找主轴了
keep looking for the road.
我知道  再等我一下行吗
I know. Just -- just give me a minute, okay?
-迪恩  - 萨姆  拜托了  再等一下
- Dean  - Sam, please. One minute.
喂
Hello?
不行  约翰
No, John.
我不想再谈论这件事了
We're not having this conversation again.
有什么需要考虑的
Time to think about what?
家里有两个孩子在等你
You have two boys at home.
我记得这件事
I remember this.
爸妈大吵一架
Mom and dad were fighting,
之后爸爸就搬出去住了几天
and then he moved out for a couple days.
爸爸老说他的婚姻很完美
Dad always said they had the perfect marriage.
那是在妈妈去世之后
It wasn't perfect until after she died.
好吧  那就不用了
Fine. Then don't.
我们没什么好谈的了
There's nothing more to talk about.
接下来怎么了
What happens next?
没事的妈妈
It's okay, mom.
爸爸还是爱你的
Dad still loves you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我永远都不会离开你
I'll never leave you.
你  真是我的小天使
You...are my little angel.
想吃点派吗
How 'bout some pie?
等着啊
Okay.
咋了
What?
我刚刚才发现
I just never realized
这么久都是你在帮爸爸善后
how long you've been cleaning up dad's messes.
无所谓了  咱们上路吧
Whatever. Let's keep moving.
我以前在哪见过这个
I've seen this somewhere before.
在哪
Where?
我们现在在哪
Where are we?
不是吧
No way.
骨头  嘿  过来
Bones! Hey, come here!
来  快来
Come here!
嘿  哈哈
Hey!
骨头
Bones?
是啊  骨头是我的狗狗
Yeah. Bones was my dog.
你的  你的狗
Your -- your dog?
是啊
Yeah.
这里难道是弗拉格斯塔夫
Is this Flagstaff?
是啊
Yeah.
你好呀伙计
Hey, boy!
-对你这算是一段美好的回忆啊  - 当然了
- This is a good memory for you?  - Yeah!
我终于自己住了两周
I mean, I was on my own for two weeks.
天天靠零食和饮料过活
I lived off of Funyuns and Mr. Pibb.
怎么了
What?
你已经不记得了  是吧
You don't remember, do you?
在我负责照看你的时候离家出走
You ran away on my watch.
我四处找你
I looked everywhere for you.
我还以为你已经死了
I thought you were dead.
等到爸爸回家
And when dad came home...
迪恩  我十分抱歉
Dean, look -- I'm sorry.
我没站在你的角度想过
I-I never thought about it like that.
算了吧  咱们走
Forget it. Let's roll.
别动
Stay.
小骨  别跟来
Bonesy, stay.
这又是哪段记忆
What memory is this?
我也不知道
No idea.
好吧  咱们走
All right. Come on.
迪恩
Dean...
主轴  上帝
Road, God.
记得吗
Remember?
等等  别急
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
这地方
This?
这就是你甩开我们
This is the night you ditched us
去斯坦福的那晚  对吧
for Stanford, isn't it?
你梦想的天堂就是这样吗
This is your idea of heaven?
那晚可算是我人生中最糟糕的一晚了
This was, like, one of the worst nights of my life.
我也没法控制这事
I can't control this stuff.
说真的吗
Seriously?
这对你来说是幸福的回忆吗
This is a happy memory for you?
我不知道  当时就我一个人
I don't know. I mean, I was on my own.
我终于离开了爸爸
I finally got away from dad.
是呀  你离开的可不光是他一个
Yeah, he wasn't the only one you got away from.
迪恩  真的很抱歉  我只是
Dean, I'm sorry. I-I just...
是是  我知道  你没站在我的角度想过
Oh, I know -- y-you didn't think of it like that.
-迪恩  - 行了吧
- Dean  - Come on!
你的天堂是和别人一起过感恩节
Your heaven is somebody else's thanksgiving, okay?
是扔下你自己的家人
It's bailing on your family.
你还想让我说什么
What do you want me to say?
兄弟
Look, man...
从来都没人帮我切过面包的边
I never got the crusts cut off my PB&J.
我
I...
只是我看待家庭的角度和你不同
I-I just don't look at family the way you do.
是啊  可我是你的家人啊
Yeah, but I'm your family.
-我知道  - 我们应当是一个整体
- I know  - We're supposed to be a team.
就算全世界与我为敌  你也应该站我这边
It's supposed to be you and me against the world, right?
迪恩  是这样啊
Dean...it is.
是吗
Is it?
走  快走  快跑
Go! Go! Go!
躲避天使
Running from angels...
用跑的
on foot...
还是在天堂
in heaven.
这么有创意
With out-of-the-box thinking like that,
你们没能阻止天启真是让我惊讶
I'm surprised you boys haven't stopped the Apocalypse already.
伙计们  有什么问题吗
Guys, what's the problem?
我只是想把你们送回人间  仅此而已
I just want to send you back to earth. That's all.
我的意思是
I mean, that is,
当然要等我重新建立一个世界之后
after I tear you a cosmos of new ones.
你们现在在我地盘上了  小子们
You're on my turf now, boys.
等到我玩够你们的时候
and by the time I'm through with you,
你们会求着说"同意"的
you're gonna be begging to say "Yes."
小子们  别傻了
Guys, come on.
躲得了初一躲不了十五
You can run, but you can't run.
快  这边走
Hurry! This way!
等等  你是谁
Wait -- Who are you?
早上好啊  小贱人们
Buenos dias, bitches.
阿瑟
Ash?
欢迎来到我的蓝色天堂
Welcome to my blue heaven.
我的天  那家酒馆
My God, the road house.
甚至连味道都没变
It even smells the same.
啤酒  血液  还有下酒菜
Bud, blood, and beer nuts --
世界上最好闻的味道了
It's the best smell in the world.
来杯冰的吧
How 'bout a cold one?
在这儿  喝不醉的
Up here, no hangover.
那
So...
别介意
I mean, no offense --
像我这种邋遢鬼死后怎么还能上天堂
How's a dirtbag like me end up in a place like this?
吾乃得救赎者  伙计
I been saved, man.
我可是首席训蛇人
I was my congregation's number-one snake handler.
这就是你所谓的天堂吗
A-and you said this was your heaven?
没错  我私人  专属的
Yep. My own...Personal.
所以天使们紧咬着我们不放时  我们是
And when the angels jumped us, we were...
是在你们的天堂
In your heaven.
也就说有两个天堂咯
So there are two heavens?
不  有超多个
No, more like 100 billion.
所以  别担心
So, no worries.
要追到你们可得费点儿神
It'll take them angel boys a minute to catch up.
什么
Wha...
你们别以为天堂是一个地方
See, you got to stop thinking of heaven as one place.
更像是好多地方挤在一起
It's more like a buttload of places all crammed together.
就像迪斯尼乐园那种
Like Disneyland,
除了没那些反犹太教徒
Except without all the anti-semitism.
迪斯尼乐园吗
Disneyland?
没错  你们有温切斯特乐园
Yeah, see, you got winchesterland...
而这是阿瑟乐园
Ashland...
而这些每一个独立乐园
A whole mess of everybody-else-lands.
拼凑在一起  就成了天堂  明白吗
Put 'em all together -- heaven, right?
而在各色乐园的中心都有一个梦幻国度
At the center of it all is the magic kingdom --
花园
The garden.
也就说每个人都在天堂中有一席位
So everybody gets a little slice of paradise?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
少数的会共享  那是特殊情况  等等
Few people share -- special cases, what not.
特殊情况  是什么意思
What do you mean, "Special"?
你明白  像
Oh, you know, like...
灵魂伴侣
Soul mates.
总的来说
Anyways...
大部分人没法离开他们那块地儿
Most people can't leave their own private idahos.
但你不是那部分人
But you ain't most people.
是的  他们可没我这能耐
Nope. They ain't got my skills.
该死的  我已经转了个遍了
Hell, I have been all over --
见到过约翰尼·卡什  巨人安德雷
Johnny Cash... Andre the giant...
还有爱因斯坦
Einstein.
萨姆  那家伙能调出白俄鸡尾酒
Sam, that man can mix a white Russian.
有一天  我碰到麦尔纳格·瓦茨亚亚那
Hell, the other day, I found mallanaga vatsyayana's.
谁来着
Who?
《性爱圣经》的作者
Wrote "The kama sutra."
那个人的天堂  销魂软骨啊
That boy's heaven -- oh, sweaty, confusing.
这话竟出自曾睡在台球桌上的家伙之口
All this from a guy who used to sleep on a pool table.
没错  如今我死了  又复活了
Yeah, now that I'm dead, I'm livin', man --
而且活得更加精彩
A whole lot more.
那你怎么找到我们的
So, how'd you find us?
我组装了一台唯我仅有的
I rigged up my very own...
神音波频侦查扫描仪
Holy rollin' police scanner.
是天使的声音  在说以诺语
That's angels, blabbin' enochian, okay?
我都听得懂
I'm fluent.
我听到你俩上来了
I heard that you were up.
当然我不得不去找你们  又一次
Course I had to come find you -- again.
再一次
Again?
因为这已经不是你们第一次上来了
Ain't the first time you been here.
你们俩是我见过死过最多回的人
I mean, you boys die more than anyone I have ever met.
是嘛
Really?
对啊  你们根本就不记得
Ah, yeah. You don't remember.
老天  一定是天使们给你们洗脑了
God! Angels -- must have windexed your brains.
那你找到其他人了吗
So, uh, I mean, have you found anybody else?
比如埃伦和乔
Ellen and jo?
埃论和乔都死了
Ellen and jo are dead?
是的  已经有几个月了
Uh, yeah. Yeah, a few months now.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
她们是在战斗中死的吗
Uh, they went down fightin'?
是的  战斗到了最后一刻
Yeah -- to the end.
没错  牺牲得相当值
Yeah, a lot of good it did.
我们的亲人呢
How about our folks?
我一直在找约翰·温切斯特
Been lookin' all over for John Winchester.
玛丽也是
Mary too.
目前为止  都一无所获
So far, nada.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不过  倒是有个人
But, hey, there is somebody
我知道她很想和你俩聊聊
Who I know for sure wants to jaw with you.
稍等
Hold up.
帕梅拉
Pamela.
很高兴能再见到你们
Nice to see you boys again.
你就是靠这个来去自如的吗
So, this is how you get around up here?
差不多
Mm. More or less.
终于能实际运用弦理论
It's just awesome to finally have an application --
真是超赞
A practical application for string theory.
那么
So...
怎么样
这一下你报复你让我被杀
That's for getting me killed.
没错
Yeah.
打一下  还算轻的
That's...Probably less than I deserve.
如果能让你好受点儿的话
If it makes you feel any better,
阿瑟也是被我们害死的
we got Ash killed, too.
我无所谓啊
I'm cool with it.
他无所谓
He's cool with it.
那么  你呢  还好吗
So, I mean... Are you good?
很好啊
I'm good.
真的
Really.
我还记得死前的那一幕
Remember my death scene --
挨了一刀  口吐鲜血
Gutshot, coughing blood?
你还对我说我能到更好的地方去
You told me I was going someplace better.
-我瞎掰的  - 你说得没错
- I was lying.  - You were right.
我的天堂  俨然世外桃园的无尽版
My heaven -- it is one long show at the meadowlands.
真是棒极了  你该来见识一下
It's amazing. You should see it.
没错
Yeah.
你不相信我说的吗
You don't believe me.
相信  我相信  只不过
No, I do. I-it's just, you know...
无止尽的困在你那个天使掌控的
Spending eternity trapped in your own little universe
小小的世界里  太寂寞了
while the angels run the show -- that's lonely.
那  那根本就算不上天堂
You know, that's -- that's not nirvana.
那  更像是黑客帝国
That's...The matrix.
我不清楚
I don't know.
天堂至少比地狱好吧
Attic's still better than the basement.
是没错  但
Yeah, but...
瞧瞧这地方
You know, this place --
感觉虽然真实  但毕竟只是个复制品
It feels real, but it's memorex.
最真实的世界是在下面
Real is down there.
对的  很接近了
Yeah, well, close enough.
听着  迪恩  我很快乐
Look, Dean, I'm happy.
我很平静
I'm at peace.
干嘛  想让我也住进来吗
What, you trying to sell me a timeshare?
到底什么意思
I mean, what's with the pitch?
我知道米迦勒
I know that Michael
想利用你的身体
Wants to take you out for a test drive.
-帕梅拉  - 说说而已
- Pamela - Just saying.
要是你和他合作会怎样
What happens if you play ball with him --
最坏的情况
Worst case?
很多人会死
A lot of people die.
然后他们会到这里来  这样不好吗
And then they come here. That really so bad?
听着  也许
Look...Maybe...
你不用这么艰苦地战斗
You don't have to fight it so hard.
这就是我想说的
That's all I'm trying to say.
找到了去花园的捷径
Found a shortcut to the garden.
耶
Oh, yeah!
所有可以去梦幻国度的途径
All-access pass to the magic kingdom.
很好
Good.
不好吗
Not good?
那个撒迦利亚同学会监视
That Zach fella's gonna be watching
每条通向花园的路
Every road to the garden.
小心点
So watch your ass.
还有  迪恩
And, Dean...
正如我所幻想的
Just how I imagined.
先生们
Gentlemen.
不是想打击你们  但是
I don't mean to be a downer or anything, but, uh...
我肯定不久就会再见到你们
I'm sure I'll see you again soon.
那就给我们留一盒冰啤酒吧
Well, keep a sixer on ice for us.
好
Yeah.
这是
What the...
我们怎么回家了
Why are we back home?
不知道
I don't know.
我们接下来怎么办
So, what are we gonna do?
我想还是继续找主轴吧
Keep looking for the road again, I guess.
宝贝  你怎么起来了
Honey? Why are you up?
听着  对不起
Look, I'm -- I'm -- I'm sorry.
我爱你  但你不是真实的
I love you... But you're not real.
我们没有时间了
And we don't have time --
你做噩梦了吗
Did you have a nightmare?
告诉我
Tell me.
我得走了
I got to go.
那我来告诉你我的噩梦怎么样  迪恩
Then how about I tell you my nightmare, Dean?
我被烧死的那晚
The night I burned.
小萨姆  我们快离开这里
Sammy, let's get out of here.
不准离开我
Don't you walk away from me.
我从来没有爱过你
I never loved you.
你是我的负担
You were my burden.
你束缚了我
I was shackled to you.
看看我经历了什么
Look what it got me.
迪恩
Dean.
最糟糕的是气味
The worst was the smell.
至于痛楚
The pain, well...
皮肤都烫到起泡了还能说什么呢
What can you say about your skin bubbling off?
但是那个气味实在是
But the smell was so...
那一刹那
You know, for a second,
我以为烤箱里面的炖肉烧焦了
I thought I left a pot roast burning in the oven.
但是  那是我的肉
But...It was my meat.
然后  我终于死了
And then, finally, I was dead.
不幸中的万幸就是
The one silver lining...
我终于离开你了
Is that at least I was away from you.
每个人都离你而去  迪恩  你注意到了吗
Everybody leaves you, Dean. You noticed?
妈妈
Mommy...
爸爸
Daddy.
甚至是萨姆
Even Sam.
你有问过自己原因吗
You ever ask yourself why?
也许不是他们的问题
Maybe it's not them.
也许  是你的问题
Maybe...It's you.
现在放轻松点  宝贝
Easy, now, kitten.
是你干的好事儿
You did this.
我才刚开始
And I'm just getting started.
伙计们  你们真的认为
I mean, guys, did you really think
可以避开我偷偷溜到花园里吗
You could just sneak past me into mission control?
混蛋
You son of a bitch.
萨姆  我也会对你说同样的话
You know, I'd say the same thing about you, sam,
但实际上我很喜欢你妈妈
But I have actually grown quite fond of your mother.
或者  至少是记忆中的她
Or, at least, the blessed memory of her.
我想我们一定会共度很多美好时光
I think we're gonna be logging a lot of quality time together.
我发觉她真是
I've discovered she's quite the...
性感熟女
Milf.
你就自己得意吧  混蛋
You can gloat all you want, you dick.
你仍然是个秃子
You're still bald.
在天堂  我有6个翅膀和4张脸
In heaven, I have six wings and four faces,
其中一个是狮子
One of which is a lion.
你看见这张脸是因为你们
You see this because you're...
能力有限
...Limited.
我们讲点实质的  好吗
Let's brass-tack this, shall we?
你还想对我们性虐直到我们说同意
What, are you're gonna ball-gag us until we say "Yes"?
我倒听过这种调调
Huh? Yeah, I've heard that tune.
我想做的不止这些
I'm gonna do a lot more than that.
我都想好咋折腾你们了  扶他起来
I've cleared my schedule. Get him up.
告诉你吧
Let me tell you something.
我曾经功成名就
I was on the fast track once.
一直都是每月最佳员工
Employee of the month every month -- forever.
我走过大厅时  我是众人的焦点
I'd walk these halls, and people would avert their eyes!
我受人尊敬
I had respect!
然后他们让我解决你们的问题
And then they assigned me you.
现在看看我
now look at me.
我竟然不能解决
I can't close the deal
几个穿着法兰绒的可怜虫
On a couple of pathetic, flannel-wearing maggots?
大家都嘲笑我
Everybody's laughing at me.
他们是对的
And they're right to do it.
那么  无论你们答应还是不答应
So...Say yes, don't say yes.
我还是要折磨报复你们
I'm still gonna take it out of your asses.
现在是私人恩怨了  小伙们
It's personal now, boys.
我将成为这个世界上
And the last person in the history of creation
你们最可怕的敌人
You want as your enemy is me.
我告诉你们原因  路西法也许很强
And I'll tell you why -- Lucifer may be strong,
但我
But I'm...
卑鄙
Petty.
我会成为你们的"守护"天使
I'm gonna be the angel on your shoulder
直到永远
For the rest of eternity.
抱歉  先生
Excuse me, sir?
我正在办事呢
I'm in a meeting.
非常抱歉
I'm sorry.
我要跟他俩说几句话
I need to speak to those two.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我知道这不合时宜
It's a bad time, I know.
但恐怕我得坚持这点
But I'm afraid I have to insist.
还轮不到你来坚持什么
You don't get to insist jack squat.
是的  你说得对
No, you're right.
但  老大要坚持
But the boss does.
这是他的旨意
His orders.
你在说谎
You're lying.
这件事可是真的
Wouldn't lie about this.
你大可以杀了我
Look... Fire me, if you want.
他迟早会回家来的
Sooner or later, he's gonna come back home.
你也知道盛怒之下他会如何
And you know how he is with that whole "Wrath" thing.
这就是  天堂花园吗
This is...heaven's garden?
我觉得还算不错
It's nice...ish. I guess.
眼之所见乃你们心中所想
You see what you want to here.
有人看见神的王座之殿
For some it's god's throne room.
有人看见伊甸园
For others it's eden.
你俩的话  我想
You two, I believe
应该是克里夫兰植物园
It's the cleveland Botanical gardens.
你俩曾来此野游
You came here on a field trip.
你是约书亚
You're Joshua.
正是
I'm Joshua.
你与上帝交谈吗
So you talk to god?
通常是他与我交谈
Mostly, he talks to me.
我们有话要对他说
We need to speak to him.
事态紧急
It's important.
-他在哪儿  - 地球上
- Where is he?  - On earth.
-在干什么  - 我不知道
- Doing what?  - I don't know.
地球上哪里
Where on earth?
抱歉  我们基本上不是面对面交谈
No. Sorry. We don't exactly speak face-to-face.
对不起  我不太明白
I'm sorry. I...I don't get it.
上帝不与任何人对话  那
God's not talking to nobody, so...
那他为什么跟我说话
So why is he talking to me?
有时我觉得是因为我心存怜悯
I sometimes think it's because I can sympathize --
能感同身受
gardener to gardener.
通过我们之间的联系  我觉得他很孤独
And between us, I think he is lonely.
我可真为他心碎
My heart's breaking for him.
你能至少给我们传个话吗
Can you... at least get him a message for us?
其实他给你们带话了
Actually, he has a message for you.
"放弃吧"
"Back off."
什么
What?
他已经知道了  所有你们要说的话
He knews already. Everything you want to tell him.
他知道天使们的所作所为
He knows what the angels are doing.
他知道世界末日已经开启
He knows that the apocalypse has begun.
他只是不觉得这是他的问题
He just doesn't think it's his problem.
不是他的问题吗
Not his problem?
上帝已经对你们施予救赎
God saved you already.
让你们登上那飞机  救回了卡西迪奥
He put you on that plane. He brought back castiel.
他施恩让你们在天堂得救
He granted you salvation in heaven.
在你们做出那一切后  他还是一样
And after everything you've done, too.
很久以前这就已经与他无关了
It's more than his intervened in a long time.
他职责已尽
He's finished.
不管有没有魔法护符
Magic amulet or not,
你们都找不到他
you won't be able to find him.
但他能让事情结束  他能结束一切
But he can stop it. He could stop all of it.
确实  但他不会这么做
I suppose he could, but he won't.
为什么
Why not?
他当初为何会容忍恶魔存在呢
Why does he allow evil in the first place?
你能动动愚蠢的脑子  想想这些问题
You could drive yourself nuts asking questions like that.
那他就这么袖手旁观  隔岸观火吗
So he's just gonna sit back and watch the world burn?
我知道这对你有多重要  迪恩
I know how important this was to you, Dean.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
算了
Well, forget it.
就又一个满嘴借口
Just another deadbeat dad
不负责任的老头  是吗
with a bunch of excuses, right?
我习惯了
I'm used to that.
我会一样应付过去的
I'll muddle through.
可你不知道  这次你是否能成功
Except you don't know if you can this time.
你杀不死路西法的
You can't kill the devil.
你正失去信念
And you're losing faith --
失去自我和兄弟  现在又变成这样
and yourself, your brother, and now this.
上帝是你最后的希望
God was your last hope.
我只是
I just...
我真希望事情不是这样
I wish I could tell you something different.
我们怎么知道你说的是真话呢
How do we know you're telling the truth?
你觉得我会说谎吗
You think that I would lie?
只不过
But it's just...
你可不是我们见过的第一个天使
You're not exactly the first angel we've met.
我站在你们那边  孩子
I'm rooting for you boys.
我希望我能帮助你们  真的
I wish I could do more to help you. I do.
但  我只整理树篱
But... I just trim the hedges.
那现在怎么办
So, what now?
你们再次回家
You go home again.
恐怕这次和上次不一样了
I'm afraid this time won't be like the last.
这次
This time
上帝希望你们
God wants you
铭记一切
to remember.
你还好吗
You all right?
怎么样算"还好"
Define "All right."
可能
Maybe...
可能约书亚在说谎
Maybe Joshua was lying.
我不这么认为  卡西
I don't think he was, cass.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
我曾相信...
I believed in...
我不再需要这个了
I don't need this anymore.
这毫无价值
It's worthless.
卡西  等等
Cass. Wait.
我们会找到办法的
We'll find another way.
我们还是能阻止这一切的
We can still stop all this, dean.
怎么阻止
How?
不知道
I don't know.
但我们会找到办法的
But we'll find it.
你和我
You and me.
我们会找到的
We'll find it.